Guide to the Yale Daily News Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographic negatives used in the publication of the Yale Daily News, 1957-1982; Series I
  - 1979
    - 1979 November 2-30
      - Soccer v. Harvard, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Intramural Athletics, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Water Polo, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Water Polo v. Harvard, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Football v. Harvard, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Women's Basketball v. Fairfield, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Water Polo Championship, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Squash v. Fordham, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - 1979 December 1-9
      - Undergraduate art exhibit at AandA building, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Wrestling v. Nutben, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Hockey v. Cornell, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Wrestling v. Rutgers, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Hockey v. Taft, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Squash v. Stony Brook, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Basketball v. Fordham, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Judo Practice, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Hockey v. Maine, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Men's and Women's Fencing v. Cornell, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Women's Hockey v. Princeton, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Basketball v. Holy Cross, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Women's Basketball v. Holy Cross, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Wrestling v. Navy, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Swimming v. Columbia, 1979 December (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - 1980
    - 1980 January 10-30
      - Dance Marathon at Calhoun, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Judith Sillivam Non-Smoking Club, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Fire on Edwards Street, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Graduate/Professional Student Senate, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Yale Polo Club, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Weather report (jazz group) at Woolsey Hall, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Yale Cabaret, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Caligula at York Square Theater, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Dotie's Home (Yale Cabaret), 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - ES play-Phoenix, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Basketball v. Harvard, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Intramural Basketball Shoot-Off, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Squash v. Trinity, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Women's Swimming v. S. Conn, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Women's Basketball v. Manhattan, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Women's Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Women's Swimming v. Dartmouth, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Wrestling v. New Hampshire, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Basketball v. New Hampshire, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Hockey v. Hotchkiss, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Women's Squash v. Dartmouth, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Basketball v. Fairfield, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Wrestling, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Women's Swimming v. RI, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Men's Swimming v. Cornell, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Men's Fencing v. Cornell, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Hockey v. Providence, 1980 January (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - 1980 February 1-16
      - Assorted Exits, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Yale Cabaret bouncer, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Jazz band in Davenport dining hall, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Ladies in Waiting at Dramat, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Miss Julie- BK dramat, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Balloons from Calhoun, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Yale Cabaret-Don't Touch That Dial, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Protest photo at Basketball game, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Bush Campaign? John Anderson Birthday party?, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Pee Wee Hockey, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Men's Squash v. BU, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Berkeley Hockey v. SM, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Hockey v. UNH, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Squash v. Navy, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Basketball v. Navy, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Women's Basketball v. Navy, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Women's Hockey, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Women's Squash v. Trinity, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Hockey v. BU, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Women's Gymnastics v. Conn, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Men's Volleyball, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Swimming v. Springfield, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Volleyball v. U Mass, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Wrestling v. U of Penn, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Women's Hockey v. Harvard, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Hockey v. UVM, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Gymnastics, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Women's Squash House Cup, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Basketball v. Brown, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Women's Hockey v. U Conn, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Basketball v. Penn, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - 1980 February 17-28
      - Trouble in Tahiti-Yale Dramat Experimental Theater, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Dance Concert in Morse, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Ezra Stiles Little Theater Pushebeard Players, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - play: Don't Drink the Water, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - BK Dramat- Poor Murder, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Cabaret, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - ½ roll: JE Sux sign and cups, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Angie Bassett and Hillory Mesherees student theatrical directors, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Very Good Eddie (in TD dining hall), 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - The Front Page- Pierson Dramat, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Circle (play) Ezra Stiles dining hall, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - TD dramat Very Good Eddie, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - She Loves Me-Trumbull play, Cabaret, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Talking Feet in Branford, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - YCC meeting, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Men's and Women's Gymnastics, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Basketball v. Union, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Women's Squash v. Harvard, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Basketball v. Columbia, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Swimming v. Harvard, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Men's and Women's Fencing v. Harvard, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Women's basketball v. Harvard, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Basketball v. Cornell, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Squash v. Harvard, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Hockey v. Harvard, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Hockey v. Princeton, 1980 February (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - 1980 March 1-29
      - Charities Drive raffle drawing, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Composer concert at TD, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Town meeting (top admin. brass), 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Short Eyes (play at the Afro-Am Center), 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Yale Cabaret Dorothy Parker Review, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Funeral Games-Nicholas Chapel, Trumbull, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Freshman one-acts: Ezra Stiles Little Theater, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Guff at Calhoun (student band), 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Voter Registration, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Basketball v. Harvard Tournament, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Lacrosse v. U Conn, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Lacrosse v. Johns Hopkins, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Men's Gymnastics v. S. Conn, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Men and Women's Light Weight Crew, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. Dartmouth, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Women's Crew v. Penn and Conn College, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Tennis v. Penn, 1980 March (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - 1980 April 2-29
      - Gillbert and Sullivan Play, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Arts Sculpture, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Scapino-Dramat, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Hang Gliding, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Tap Night-Secret Society, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Crew Derby Day, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Sunny Day, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Writers of TV show, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Journalist Panel, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Blood Drive for Magazine, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Rosencrantz and Guildenstein are Dead-Morse, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - College Bowl, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Balleywrack Theater; Zymurgy- in Little Theater, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Yale Cabaret- Story of My Ugly Man, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Charities Drive Auction, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Cricket, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - God Smoke at Dramat, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Play at Pierson- Sexual Perversity in Chicago, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - The Green Room- Trumbull College, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Female Transport- Play at Trumbull, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Robber Bridegroom- D-port dining hall, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Royal Lichtenstein Circus, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Cabaret, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Scenes from a Marriage, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Cross Campus Tang (beer drinking contest), 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Dancers for ES performance, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Women's Tennis v. Trenton St., 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Women's Softball v. Bridgeport, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Men's Track and Field, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Tennis v. Columbia, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Women's Crew, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Men's Heavy Weight Crew, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Basketball v. S Conn, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Lacrosse v. Williams, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Women's Tennis v. Princeton, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Women's Track v. Harvard and Princeton, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. Penn, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Women's Softball v. Army, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Women's Track v. Harvard, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Tennis v. Penn, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Women's Tennis v. Brown, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. RI, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Golf v. Brown, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Lacrosse v. Harvard, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Track v. Princeton, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Basketball v. Fairfield, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Women's Rugby v. Tufts and Brown, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. Harvard, 1980 April (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - 1980 May 6-24
      - Commencement Show, 1980 May (Box 10, Folder 99)
      - Shots around Yale, 1980 May (Box 10, Folder 99)
      - Class Day 1980, Old Campus, 1980 May (Box 10, Folder 99)
      - Deja Revue cast, 1980 May (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - 1980 September 2-30
      - Opening Day, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Freshman Assembly, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Tommy and the Yale Musical Group personnel, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - JE picnic, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Bellboys (band), 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Unfinished heating unit at Silliman, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Students for Anderson Meeting, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - America's Cup, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - play: The Birds, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Saybrook golf, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Fritz Cup, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Bruce Springsteen Concert line at Cutler's, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Cyrons- for Denerdis, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Silliman Dramatic Attic, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Football v. U Conn, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Women's Soccer, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Soccer v. Conn, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Rugby v. Conn Yankees, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Football Scrimmage v. Montclair St, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Women's Cross Country, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Soccer, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Dwight Hall Jamboree, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Men and Women's Cross Country v. Central Conn, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Soccer v. Stanford, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Tennis Practice, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Varsity Tennis, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Football v. Brown, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Women's Soccer v. Brown, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Field Hockey Practice, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Water Polo v. UCLA, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Intramural Swimming, 1980 September (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - 1980 October 1-31
      - Yale Band on Cross Campus, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Cricket, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Architecture Graduate Show at AandA, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - BAC children's art tour, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Jazz Ensemble, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Dance Marathon, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - 5th floor Payne Whitney Gym- weight lifting machines, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Columbus Day Parade, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Canadian Thanksgiving dinner-JE, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - The Glass Menagerie, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Sailing, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Yale Mime Troupe, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - AYA, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Yowsah Meeting, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Dart Gun- for Assassin, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - actors in BK play: God, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - apple picking, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - PU debate: gun control, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Paul Rosenblatt railroad exhibit at AandA, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Random notes, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Football team on bus after Penn game, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Michael Choi going to Tae Kwon Do, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - National Championships, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Halloween Shots, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Pal Joey, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Soccer v. Conn, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Women's Volleyball, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Football v. Airforce, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Rugby v. Fairfield Univ., 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Women's Field Hockey v. Cornell, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Soccer v. Providence, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Women's Soccer v. Smith, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Women's Field Hockey v. U Mass, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Football v. Boston College, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Field Hockey v. U Conn, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Football v. Columbia, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Tailgating Columbia, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Soccer v. Columbia, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Women's Soccer v. Princeton, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Football v. Army, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Football v. Penn, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Soccer v. Fairfield, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Women's Soccer v. Dartmouth, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - 1980 November 1-22
      - Walking tour of New Haven, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - New art studios, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Stiles election debate, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Harvey, Calhoun Dramat, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Gilbert and Sullivan dress rehearsal, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Cometrons, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - God, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Building- sop (fireman by himself), 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Kiss Me Kate, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - BAC children's art tour, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Painting at Charles Seymour (B. dining hall), 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Yale Boss Mess and Econ., 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Pasteboned Players (Shawn Haggard), 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Fantastics- play in TC, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Six Rooms- play at Saybrook, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - non-violence study group, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Trumbull prod. at Mr. John chap., 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Sculpture show at Hammond Hall, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Cabaret shots, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Fresh Water, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Women's Soccer v. Princeton, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Women's Rugby v. Dartmouth, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Bladderball, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Football v. Cornell, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Soccer v. Cornell, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Football v. Princeton, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Soccer v. Princeton, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Squash Exhibition- Victor Wagner, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Soccer v. Harvard, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Harvard Game, 1980 November (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - 1980 December 1-21
      - Creations, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Smuggles puzzle, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Berlin to Broadway- Kurt Well Review, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Production in Trumbull- dress rehearsal, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Sweet Charity, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Snow shots (first snow of 1980), 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Amateur night visitors, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Shot of empty room, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Photo essay for magazine, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Freshman Christmas Banquet, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - AI sign December 20 research computer, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Women's Swimming Coaches, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Women's Swimming v. Brown, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Squash v. Stony Brook, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Hockey v. St. Laurel, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Basketball v. U Conn, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Wrestling v. West Point, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Women's Hockey v. U Conn, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Swimming v. Columbia, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Basketball v. Conn, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Hockey v. Swedish Jr. Nationals, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Squash v. Fordham, 1980 December (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - 1981
    - 1981 January 12-31
      - Peirson Film Society (people buying tickets), 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Yale Cabaret An Evening Wasted and Tom, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - 20 Yale Artists, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Yale Concerto competition (grads), 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Hockey v. Cornell, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Women's Basketball, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Hockey v. Princeton, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Basketball v. Brown, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Women's Swimming v. Rutgers, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Women's Squash v. Brown, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Booby Brook (Hockey), 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - JV Hockey v. Contesbury, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Women Weight Lifting, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Squash v. Williams, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Men's Swimming v. Army, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Basketball v. Manhattan, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Squash v. Dartmouth, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Basketball v. Northrop, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Men's Basketball, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Fencing, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Men's Indoor track, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Men's Hockey, 1981 January (Box 11, Folder 103)
    - 1981 February 3-25
      - Group work, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Waiting for Godot: Bart Teush, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Yale dramat seminar- JE library, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - One woman show, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Cabaret, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Cross Country Solo, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - The Visit, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Dartmouth Winter Carnival, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Ah, Wilderness!, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Trial By Jury, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Two Gentlemen of Verona, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Heartbreak House, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Ivy League Gymnastics Championships, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Stop the World I want to Get Off, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - No Exit- Stiles Theater, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - The Exit- Coffee house, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - German Play- Silliman Dramatic Attic, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Berkeley Play: Tragedy of the Trojan Women, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Tentative Plans- Mike Kaplan, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Fencing, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Women's Basketball v. Princeton, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Basketball v. Union, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Women's Hockey v. Brown, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Women's Fencing, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Women's Squash: Howe Cup tournament, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)